Are you tired of
bulky old vacuum cleaners?
Ouch!
I've had it with this old thing.
There must be a better way!
Oh, but there is!
Meet Alex!
The space aged cleaning solution!
Alex knows how to clean those
hard to reach places!
I won't be needing this anymore!
No! you won't.
Because Alex is
the future of clean!
Cut!
That's a wrap, folks!
Let's call it a day.
Achoo!
Yikes!
Gazuntite!
Pardon me, Sorry to disturb you, sir.
The name's Alex.
Oh, I know who you are.
My name is Tumbo,
and I'm a huge fan!
Oh, really, Tumbo?
Oh, seriously...
You've got all these modes, no cord!
You got arms!
You're so cool!
They don't call me "the future of clean" for noth...
...ing.
I had to clean that up.
You were saying?
I think you were saying
that I was amazing. I was gonna say...
Achoo!
Gazuntite.
Oh well,
- I'm a little clogged up.
- You know, you might wanna hold off on the vacuuming.
- Achoo!
- Gazuntite.
Because everytime you vacuum.
- Achoo!
- Gazuntite.
You sneeze back out.
- Achoo!
- Gazuntite.
You're not listening.
Pay attention to me!
Achoo!
Gazuntite.
I am so sorry Alex!
Le-Let me get that.
Wow...
Awesome!
Okay, Tumbo!
What do you say, we have some quiet time.
Great idea, Alex.
Some vacuums are super loud...
and I'm like put a sock in it.
Except, not literally...
a sock in a tube would restrict...
- air flow and...
-Tumbo.
Quiet time.
Alright. Yeah, Okay
Oops..
Oh, I got it.
No no no no no! Allow me!
No no! But it's my responsiblity.
- It's my pleasure!
- But I insist...
But I said...
it's my pleasure!
Ah, That's better!
I can't move, Alex.
I guess that why...
I'm the future of clean...
...not you!
I got it.
Uh-oh.
Hold it! Hold it in, Tumbo!
Hold it in!
Gazuntite.
Hey, Alex!
Yeah, Tumbo?
No sneezing.
You fixed my clogs!
Glad that I could help, buddy.